techly.com.au 2018-03-14

# Privacy Policy - Techly

As used in this Privacy Policy, “Techly” refers to all websites (including Techly.com.au), mobile sites, applications, social media, and other properties or services owned or operated by Conversant Media, Pty Ltd.

By visiting Techly, viewing our content and/or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

******What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?**

This Privacy Policy is part of Techly’s Terms of Service and covers the treatment of user information, including Personally Identifiable Information (defined below), obtained by Techly, including information obtained when you access or log in to Techly, and/or register for content or events provided by Techly.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Techly does not own or control, or to individuals whom Techly does not employ or manage, including any of the third parties to which Techly may disclose user information as set forth in this Policy.

**What Types of User Information Does Techly Obtain?**

Techly may obtain the following types of information from you or concerning your computer or device (“Information”), which may include information that can be used to identify you as specified below (“Personally Identifiable Information”):

  * Name
  * Email Address
  * Blog or Website URL
  * Social Networking Handle or Username
  * Photo
  * Demographic Information (e.g., age, gender, interests, and preferences)
  * Activities or Content Viewed on Techly
  * Information Collected Automatically (detailed below)
  * Information Received from Third Parties (detailed below)

In certain cases, we may request that you provide some of the Information identified above in order to obtain specific products or services (such as registering for a Techly profile). If you choose not to provide the Information we request, you may still use Techly, but you may be unable to access certain features or services.

When you register to receive any products or services from Techly or provide information to Techly in any other manner, you agree to provide only true, accurate, current and complete information.

**Information Collected Automatically**

Techly may automatically receive and log certain types of information when you visit or interact with our websites, services, mobile applications or other products, including:

  * Browser Information
  * Operating System Information
  * Mobile Device Information (e.g., device identifier, mobile operating system, etc.)
  * IP Address
  * Internet Service Provider
  * Content Viewed
  * Geographic Location
  * Connection Speed
  * Time of Visit
  * Referring Site, Application, or Service
  * Registration Time

**Information Received From Third Parties**

**Third Party Websites/Social Networking Sites**

If you choose to use any third party website or service that is integrated with Techly, including a third party social networking or blogging site, such as LinkedIn, Facebook, Twitter or Instagram (“Third Party Websites”)—or if you use any Techly application provided through any Third Party Website—we may receive Information, including Personally Identifying Information, from such Third Party Websites, including, but not limited to:

  * Name
  * Nickname or Username
  * Photo or Graphic Avatar
  * Unique Third Party Website Identifier (e.g., Facebook User ID)
  * Biographical or Demographic Information (e.g. professional title, gender, college attended, etc.)
  * Likes and Interests
  * Contacts/Friends/Associations
  * Any Information That Is Publicly Available on Third Party Websites

For example, Techly may offer the ability to use certain Third Party Websites to facilitate your registration on Techly. We may also use information about your profile and connections on Third Party Websites to allow you to share or connect with your friends and contacts on Techly or to personalize your experience. In addition, Techly offers “plug ins” and “widgets” from various Third Party Websites that allow you to share Techly content off of our service.

Your decision to use, or share with, a Third Party Website when accessing or using Techly products and services is completely voluntary. Techly is not responsible for compliance with the policies or practices of any Third Party Website. You should ensure that you are comfortable with the information such Third Party Websites may make available to Techly by reviewing those Websites’ privacy policies and service terms, and by modifying your privacy settings and preferences on those Services.

Any information we receive from Third Party Websites will be governed by this Privacy Policy.

**How Do We Use This Information?**

We use the Information we obtain from or concerning you or your computer or device to provide Techly products and services, fulfill your requests, improve our products and services, personalize and tailor your experience on Techly, operate our business, and understand how users are engaging with Techly.

In addition, we may use Information from or concerning you or your computer or device to facilitate the delivery of content or advertisements that we believe may be of interest to you, or to communicate with you about new or existing products and services or special offers. For example, we may periodically send promotional materials or notifications related to our products and services to the email address associated with your account if you subscribed to the email.

**Techly’s Use of Cookies**

Techly may place “cookies” on your computer or device that may contain anonymous Information that is associated with you. Cookies are small text files a website uses to recognize users, and are typically placed on your hard disk by a web server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain (here, Techly) that issued the cookie to you or that, in some cases, can be read by a third party domain.

Our cookies may record Information about your use of Techly so that we can provide a continuous and more personalized experience for you, including for one or more of the following purposes: to help identify visitors; assess usage patterns; identify preferences; control the display of ads; diagnose problems with our servers; gather demographic information; analyze trends and usage patterns; conduct research; deliver editorial content; record registration and personalized information; and otherwise administer Techly products and services.

If you do not wish to have Techly place and use cookies on your computer, you should set your browser preferences to refuse cookies before accessing Techly. Techly is not responsible for any failure by you or your browser to accurately implement or communicate your browser preferences or settings. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of Techly that depend on cookies.

**Techly does not control and is not responsible for the use of cookies by its third party partners or advertisers**. The use of cookies by some of these third parties is discussed below (see “Third Party Advertisements” and “Analytics Services”).

**Reviewing and Modifying Your Personally Identifying Information**

We offer several ways for you to update Personally Identifying Information that is obtained and stored by Techly, or to change your account preferences on Techly:

  1. If you have an online account with Techly, you can log in and update or change your account information
  2. You may unsubscribe to any of our e-mail updates or products by following the unsubscribe instructions in the body of any message
  3. You may contact us using our contact form.

**Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**

Techly may disclose Information (including Personally Identifying Information) from or concerning you or your computer or device to third parties in the circumstances described below. By visiting, accessing, attending or using Techly’s products, services or events, you consent to the disclosure of your

Information to certain categories of third parties in the manner described below. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the policies or practices of any of these third parties.

**Service Providers**

Techly relies on third party vendors and service providers to provide support and assistance for its products, services and events (“Service Providers”), and we may disclose your Information (including Personally Identifying Information) to these Service Providers to the extent necessary to support our products, services or events, or as otherwise set forth below.

**Web Hosts**

Techly’s website services are hosted by Bulletproof, an enterprise web hosting provider. All Information obtained and stored by Techly’s websites ( see What Types of User Information Does Techly Obtain?) is processed and stored on servers that are owned and operated by Bulletproof.

**Third Party Websites**

Techly offers the ability to share Techly content on Third Party Websites, including social networking and blogging services such as LinkedIn or Facebook, through “plugins” or “widgets” (such as LinkedIn’s “in” button or Facebook’s “Like” button). When you elect to share content and information with others on Third Party Websites, Techly may transmit your Information (including Personally Identifying Information) to such Third Party Websites. This Information may be visible on the Third Party Website to anyone who has access to that content or Information. Your decision to share information in this manner is completely voluntary. You should ensure that you are comfortable with how Third Party Websites may share your Information by reviewing their privacy policies and/or modifying your privacy settings directly on those Third Party Websites.

**URL/Referrer Header Information**

When you visit Techly websites, certain information about the content or activities you have engaged in on Techly may be reflected in the Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) for the page you are viewing on Techly (i.e., the Internet “address,” commonly displayed in the browser window). For example, the date or title of an article you are viewing may appear in the URL for that page. In addition, if you are logged into a Techly account, certain account information may be visible in the URL when you visit your account on Techly. If you leave Techly to visit a third party website, including when you click on an advertisement or link or when you share information through a social plug-in, the information contained in the URL may be transmitted to the third party website by your browser.

**Advertisers and Analytics Services**

As discussed in (“Third-Party Advertising on Techly”), Techly uses third party advertisers, including ad networks, to provide advertising on its websites. In addition, as discussed in (“Analytics Services”), Techly uses third party analytics products to obtain information about how users are using and interacting with Techly. These third parties may receive Information (including Personally Identifying Information) from Techly as discussed in greater detail in (“Security and Protection of Personally Identifying Information”).

**Law Enforcement/Legal Process**

We may disclose your Information (including Personally Identifying Information) when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to comply with any law, regulation or legal request; enforce, apply, or investigate breaches of our terms of use and other agreements; respond to public requests; or protect the rights, property, user experience or safety of Techly, our employees, our users, or others. This can include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Comments and Public Posts; Sharing on Third-Party Websites**

Techly encourages active participation by users, including through comments on Techly. However, please be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Information, personal or otherwise, on Techly, that Information can be viewed, collected and used by others, including other users, search engines, advertisers, third party applications developers, and anyone with access to Techly. Techly has no control over the use, collection or disclosure of any Information that you post publicly on Techly.

**Change of Control**

If Techly, or substantially all of its assets, is acquired by another company or party, user Information will be one of the assets transferred or acquired by the purchaser. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any purchaser of Techly or its assets may continue to collect, use and disclose your Information as set forth in this Policy.

**Third-Party Advertising on Techly**

Techly may allow third party advertising serving companies, including ad networks (“Advertisers”), to display advertisements or provide other advertising services on Techly. These third party Advertisers may use techniques other than HTTP cookies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect and record demographic and other Information about you, including your activities on or off Techly. These techniques may be used directly on Techly. Please keep in mind that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these techniques, and that browser settings that block conventional cookies may have no effect on such techniques.

Advertisers may use the information collected to display advertisements that are tailored to your interests or background and/or associate such information with your subsequent visits, purchases or other activities on other websites. Advertisers may also share this information with their clients or other third parties.

**Techly has no responsibility for the technologies, tools or practices of the Advertisers that provide advertising and related services on Techly**. This Privacy Policy does not cover any collection, use or disclosure of Information by Advertisers who provide advertising and related services on Techly. These Advertisers’ information gathering practices, including their policies regarding the use of cookies and other tracking technologies, are governed entirely by their own privacy policies, not this one.

Techly currently may be using one or more of the following Advertisers to provide advertising and related services on Techly. If you would like to know about their information gathering and privacy practices, please visit the links below

Techly uses the Standard Terms and Conditions set forth by the Internet Advertising Bureau (IAB). See [Standard Terms and Conditions](http://www.iab.net/iab_products_and_industry_services/508676/tscs3)

AdMeld | [Home Page](http://www.admeld.com/) |   [Privacy Policy](http://www.admeld.com/privacy/)  
---|---|---  
Bizo | [Home Page](http://www.bizo.com/) |   [Privacy Policy](http://www.bizo.com/businessProfessionals/privacy_policy)  
Federated Media | [Home Page](http://www.federatedmedia.net/) |   [Privacy Policy](http://www.federatedmedia.net/privacy-policy/)  
Google AdSense | [Home Page](http://www.google.com/adsense/) |   [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/privacy-policy.html)  
  
**Analytics Services**

In addition, Techly uses third party analytics providers and products to obtain, compile and analyze Information (that may include Personally Identifying Information) about how users are using and interacting with Techly. Techly may provide Information (including Personally Identifying Information) to these analytics providers for the purpose of obtaining statistics and other information about how users are using and interacting with Techly. These analytics providers may use tracking techniques other than HTTP cookies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect or compile this information. These techniques may be used directly on Techly. Techly has no responsibility for the technologies, tools or practices of the third parties that providing analytics products and services to Techly. Please also keep in mind that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these techniques, and that browser settings that block conventional cookies may have no effect on such techniques.

**Nielsen Services**

Our properties may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software, which will allow you to contribute to market research, like Digital Content Ratings. To learn more about the information that Nielsen software may collect and your choices with regard to it, please see the Nielsen Digital Measurement Privacy Policy at [www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy](http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy).

**Security and Protection of Personally Identifying Information**

We have implemented reasonable security measures and practices in an effort to protect the confidentiality of your Personally Identifying Information (other than Personally Identifying Information that you have elected to disclose to others). However, no security system is impenetrable. It may be possible for third parties to intercept or access information you provide to Techly. Techly cannot guarantee the security of your Personally Identifying Information, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to Techly. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password(s) and computer or device, and to log off when using any shared computer.

**Email or Text Message Communications**

We may contact you by e-mail, text message or other equivalent electronic communications if you access Techly products or services. By visiting or using Techly content, products or services, or registering for or attending Techly events or webinars, you specifically consent to the receipt of these e-mail or text message communications. If you do not want to receive emails, text messages or other communications from us, please notify us using our contact form and include sufficient information for us to identify your account, including your Name, Email Address and the specifics of your request. If you unsubscribe, Techly may still contact you via email or text message for administrative purposes or concerning any products, services or events for which you have registered or are using.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

Techly retains the discretion to amend or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use and disclosure of Information we obtain is subject to the later of: (1) the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such Information is collected or (2) any subsequent Privacy Policy of which you have notice. Your use of Techly is entirely voluntary, and you may discontinue use of Techly at any time.

**How to Contact Us**

Techly welcomes any questions or comments you may have regarding this Privacy Policy or its implementation. Any such questions or comments should be submitted using our [contact form](http://www.techly.com.au/contact-us/) or directed to the address below. We will undertake reasonable efforts to resolve or address your concern.

**Techly**  
ATTN: Privacy  
Level 9  
46-56 Kippax Street  
Surry Hills NSW 2010

**Effective Date of this Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy is effective as of 20 January, 2014.
